[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Musa can make three payments on his bicycle. The bicycle cost him ₦3000. The first installment will be half of the cost of the bicycle. The second installment will be half of the balance. How much will Musa need to pay on his last installment?",
      "category": "A",
      "answer": 750,
      "options": "₦750___₦1000___₦150___₦250___₦2500"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "A mechanic workshop charges a customer ₦850 to repair his bike. The bike parts cost ₦50 and the remainder was for labour. If the cost of labour is ₦100 per hour, how many hours of labour did it take the mechanic workshop to repair the bike?",
      "category": "A",
      "answer": 8,
      "options": "1___7___8___4___10"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Suppose you owe ₦40 to each of four friends, ₦10 to each of three friends, and ₦100 to your parents. If two friends each owe you ₦70, what is your net debt?",
      "category": "A",
      "answer": 150,
      "options": "₦140____₦220____₦150____₦80"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "If Adamu issues 50 prepaid cards in 30 minutes, how many cards can he issue in 3 hours?",
      "category": "A",
      "answer": 300,
      "options": "400___20___600___150___300"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Mary, Bilikisu, and Amina need to prepare 500 plates of food. If Mary prepares 150 plates of food; Amina prepares 200 plates of food; how many plates of food should Bilikisu prepare?",
      "category": "A",
      "answer": 150,
      "options": "300__50__350__150__500"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Musa buys 6 sugarcanes for ₦100 each. He sells all 6 for a total of ₦1,000. How much total profit did he make?",
      "category": "A",
      "answer": 6000,
      "options": "₦600____₦900____₦300____₦400____₦6000"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What is the next number in the sequence: 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, _?",
      "category": "B",
      "answer": 21,
      "options": "21__24__34__47__52"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What is the sum of 10 and 15",
      "category": "B",
      "answer": 25,
      "options": "25__35__45__55__65"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What is the product of 5 and 7",
      "category": "B",
      "answer": 35,
      "options": "55__65__35__45__50"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What's the difference between 20 and 10",
      "category": "B",
      "answer": 10,
      "options": "45__23__21__10_5"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What is the quotient of 20 divided by 5",
      "category": "B",
      "answer": 4,
      "options": "9__5__4__3__6"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "What is the area of a square with a side length of 5cm",
      "category": "B",
      "answer": "25cm",
      "options": "75cm__40cm__25cm___34cm__90cm"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of a traditional farming method?",
      "category": "C",
      "answer": "Conventional Farming",
      "options": "Hydrophonics__Aquaphonics__Organic Farming__Vertical Farming__Conventional Farming"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "What is the primary purpose of using irrigation in agriculture?",
      "category": "C",
      "answer": "Water supply to crops",
      "options": "Pest control__Soil aeration__Weed suppression__Fertilizer application__Water supply to crops"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Which of the following is a common cereal crop",
      "category": "C",
      "answer": "Wheat",
      "options": "Tomato__Potato__Wheat__Carrot__Lettuce"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "What is the process of removing weeds from a cultivates field called ?",
      "category": "C",
      "answer": "Weed Control",
      "options": "Pollination__Fertilzation__Germination__Irrigation__Weed control"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Which farming practice involves the cultivation of fruits and vegetables without the use of synthetic fertilizers and pesticides?",
      "category": "C",
      "answer": "Organic Farming",
      "options": "Organic Farming__Intensive Farming__Subsistence farming__Commercial Farming__Precision Farming"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "What is the purpose of crop rotation in farming?",
      "category": "C",
      "answer": "Improve Soil Fertility",
      "options": "Maximize water usage__Improve soil fertility__increase crop diversity__control pest infestations__accelerate crop growth"
    }
]